-He'll be where?
-On the front steps.
[indistinct chatter]
[cars accelerate]
Whoa.
Look over there!
Guildmaster Baek
from the White Tigers!
[MALE REPORTER 1]
And Jong-in Choi
from the Hunters Guild!
This place
is crawling with press.
Any idea
what they're doing here?
Excuse me. Are the two of you
here to recruit Minsung Lee?
[YOONHO]
Who the hell is Minsung Lee?
He's not the reason I'm here,
so I have no comment.
As I understand it,
Mister Lee has already
signed a contract
with the Reaper Guild.
We have other business
to see to.
That's too bad.
Woulda really
spiced things up, you know.
[MALE REPORTER 2]
Jeez, what a waste of time.
I heard some news, by the way.
About how the Hunters Guild
ran into a little trouble
with a near S-rank gate.
It wasn't too bad,
especially not
compared to the red gate
that claimed
a rookie A-rank leader
-from the White Tigers.
-[Yoonho scoffs]
[YOONHO]
Way I hear it,
you were just
about to give us a call.
[CHOI]
Thankfully, because of him,
that wasn't necessary.
It's only right
for the Hunters Guild
to offer a very warm reception
to show our gratitude.
[YOONHO]
Oh, don't be ridiculous!
He saved our asses, too.
Plus that raid left us
down an A-rank.
So you want to fill that spot
with an S-rank?
Sounds like
you're looking to start a war?
You're one to talk!
Don't give me any of that
holier than thou crap!
[both growling]
[LIM]
Well, well...
if it isn't Jong-in and Yoonho.
Fellas.
You're not here to try to
snatch Minsung from us, are ya?
[BOTH] I told ya I don't give
a damn about Minsung
or whatever the hell
his name is!
All right, sorry I asked.
Geez, don't bite my head off.
[JINWOO]
That's a whole lotta people.
Hell's goin' on?
[STUDENT 1] Check it out!
It's Minsung's
press conference!
[STUDENT 2]
Oh, you mean that actor guy?
[STUDENT 1] Apparently,
he's like a total playboy.
-Yeah, they call him...
-Did you hear that?
Whatever it is, I don't care.
[MINSUNG] First off,
I'd like to thank you
for gathering here today.
As I'm sure you're all aware.
I, Minsung Lee,
recently awakened as a hunter.
And today is the day
of my assessment.
I've struggled
with this decision
from the moment I awakened.
But now,
I've finally made up my mind
to bravely
confront my destiny head on!
I've already spoken
to Guildmaster Tae-Gyu Lim,
and he's agreed to let me
fight for the Reaper Guild!
If you're joining a guild,
are your acting days over?
[MALE REPORTER 1] Don't you
think this is a bit premature?
[MALE REPORTER 2]
Will you mainly be focusing
on your hunter duties?
[MINSUNG]
How gullible can you be?
I've already gotten my A-rank.
My contract with the Reapers
is only for two years.
I'll dabble in hunting
long enough
for people to forget
all about my scandals.
And after that,
leverage my A-rank status
to push my acting career
back into the spotlight!
No matter
what rank I end up being,
I'm fully prepared
to fight with everything I--
[MANAGER] I'm going to need
you to stop right there!
Can't you see
all these reporters?
You're in the way!
Buzz off!
Um...I have business
with the Association.
[MANAGER]
It can wait!
[MINSUNG] How could
this idiot be so oblivious?
You can't go in
through this entrance!
-Now get out of here!
-[GUNHEE] I'm afraid
that isn't
your decision to make.
[MANAGER] Uh.
Chairman Go!
You see, this young man here
is a guest of mine.
I seem to recall asking you
to refrain
from holding a press conference
at this hour.
-[gasps] I just--
-This way.
Come along with me...
-Thought it would be
-good publicity.
-...Hunter Sung.
Argh! What the hell
am I supposed to do now?
I'll be right back,
I need to confer
with the Association.
Unfortunately, another hunter
is being assessed
at the moment.
I'm afraid
you won't be able to enter
until they're done.
[whispering]
Come on, dude.
You gotta know who I am, right?
A single word from me,
and you're out of a job,
my guy.
Sorry to say, but I don't
recognize you at all.
And if you insist
on trying to get in,
I'll have to remove you
from the premises.
[gasps]
[JINWOO]
Hm.
After hearing about today,
they came to see
your reassessment in person.
The prospect
of the first S-rank hunter
to appear in two years
has piqued their interest.
[gate whirring]
[ASSOCIATE 1] Before
we begin the reassessment,
I'd like to confirm the nature
of your hunter abilities.
Would you mind showing us
what you can do, Hunter Sung?
Well, for starters,
I can do this.
Ah, you can create
and control a summon.
So your specialty
is summoning magic, I take it?
Yeah, uh,
I guess you can say that.
[GUNHEE]
Hunter Sung.
Manager Woo has given me
detailed reports
of your abilities.
You aren't going
to hold out on us, are you?
[JINWOO]
Right,
guess the cat's out of the bag
at this point.
♪
[gasps]
I can summon
around a hundred more.
[ASSOCIATE 1]
D-did you say a hundred?
Unbelievable!
[CHOI]
His magic power is tremendous!
[YOONHO] That's enough
to overwhelm even me.
Is this guy for real?
He continues to astound me.
[ASSOCIATE 1]
Thank you for your patience.
Your reassessment
is now complete.
And here is your
updated hunter ID.
[JINWOO]
Nice.
Now I can sell
the Sphere of Avarice
with no problems.
And then I can afford
the gear I need
to clear the Demon's Castle.
[GUNHEE]
It's official.
I'd like to congratulate you
on becoming an S-rank Hunter.
I'm looking forward to seeing
what you decide to do
with that strength.
I have high hopes for you.
♪
[CHOI] It's an honor to
welcome the newest S-rank.
Perhaps you would allow me
to thank you
for your assistance?
Our guild is in your debt.
And ours too.
If you have some time to chat,
I would love to discuss
something important with you.
-Uh.
-Sorry, guys,
but I, uh, got some errands
to run right now.
Wait!
Not there!
[JINWOO] Huh?
Not where?
-[cameras clicking]
-Huh!
[gasps]
Hey, Jinah?
[JINAH]
Yeah?
Is that...
Whoa, no way.
-Stop shaking me.
-Jinwoo.
Your brother popped up
on the stream.
[JINAH] What?
Hm.
[FEMALE REPORTER]
Hunter Sung, over here, please.
[reporters clamoring]
What the heck
is happening over there?
[YOONSEOK] Hm. That kid
really did make the news.
I warned you,
but you didn't listen!
I tried telling you guys
that he had
the eyes of a killer!
There's no knowing
what messed-up stuff he's done!
[REPORTER 1] Hunter Sung
has been officially
recognized as S-rank.
[screams]
[REPORTER 1]
...certified announcement yet,
it seems his S-rank status
has been confirmed
in the Association's database!
Which would mean
Jinwoo Sung has now become
the tenth S-rank hunter
in the country!
The first to emerge
in over two years
since the awakening
of Hunter Cha!
Uhh...
[cameras clicking]
[REPORTER 2]
An S-rank?
No, wait!
But this was
-my press conference.
-[REPORTER 3] Don't let him
slip away! Come on!
[JINHO]
I wasn't able to get
Hunter Sung
to accept the offer.
That's a shame.
Hmm.
[JINWOO]
Sorry.
I can't accept.
There's still something
I gotta do on my own.
And to do it,
I need to keep fighting,
get even stronger
than I am now.
Joining an organization
would only complicate things.
Hmm.
-[JINWOO] Jinho.
-Uh?
How 'bout this instead?
[JINHO]
He, um,
he actually asked me
to join him.
[gasps]
[MYUNGHAN]
I hope you realize
how that decision
would be quite selfish.
Hmm.
[MYUNGHAN]
I had every intention
of letting Jinsung
run this operation.
But then, you came in
and begged me for a chance,
and despite all
of your extravagant claims,
you have accomplished nothing.
And now you want to run off
and work somewhere else?
You can't be serious.
I'm sorry, Father.
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to follow
Hunter Sung!
♪
[breathes shakily]
[MYUNGHAN]
I see.
Then you had best be prepared
for the consequences.
[gulps]
[GUARD 1]
Everyone, stand back!
Please keep
a reasonable distance! Hey!
[GUARD 1]
Don't push!
[YOONHO] Trust me, you don't
wanna deal with the press.
Here, why don't you let us
give you a lift home?
I'll be fine.
[gasps]
[reporters clamoring]
Despite being
a mage-type hunter,
his athletic abilities
are simply incredible.
You okay, Yoonho?
[gasps]
[YOONHO] He moved so fast
my eyes couldn't track him.
He's even stronger
than he was before.
How is that possible?
♪
[JINWOO]
It's time to gear up.
[APPRAISER 1]
Ah, Hunter Sung,
we've been expecting you.
You're in the market for
flame-resistant type artifacts,
yes?
May I inquire
about the specifics?
I need protection in
a dungeon that gets pretty hot.
[APPRAISER 1]
Oh, I don't blame you!
Well, if that's the case,
these might be
just what you're looking for.
A cape you can wear
on top of your clothes,
and a ring
that's easy to equip.
Oh, yeah, that's nice!
[APPRAISER 1] And they should
be well within your budget
at these prices.
Oh!
Could I maybe get a discount?
[appraiser 1 laughs]
[APPRAISER 1]
Well, my apologies,
but the listed prices
are the only ones
our establishment offers.
That said, you wouldn't have
to give us any money whatsoever
if you're able
to shatter this glass.
Everything in the case
would be yours.
[JINWOO]
Huh?
You see,
it's magically enhanced glass,
constructed to withstand
blows from an A-rank brawler.
[JINWOO]
This glass?
I can sense magic power,
but not that much.
[inhales deeply]
Wait, please don't do it!
I'm sorry, it was only a joke.
Even if the glass
isn't completely broken,
abnormal tremors
will summon security.
[JINWOO] Oh, my God...
I thought you...
Um, I'm so sorry!
No.
Now I see it was in poor taste.
[chuckles softly]
Well, uh,
I'm shopping for
some other stuff, too.
Like, new daggers.
[APPRAISER 2]
Excellent, sir.
If it's weaponry
that you're after
allow me to assist.
Right this way.
[footsteps receding]
Hm.
[APPRAISER 1] But,
he only prepared to punch it.
[glass cracks]
[JINWOO]
Okay, okay.
What's the price?
[APPRAISER 2]
That item.
Sells for this much.
[JINWOO]
For this?
It's only about as strong
as the Venom Fang.
Oh.
Um, hang on.
[APPRAISER 2]
Is there a problem?
[JINWOO] Nope, just
grabbing something.
How much would
this guy sell for, you think?
[APPRAISER 2]
It's certainly impressive.
I can tell the craftsman
had quite the eye for detail.
[JINWOO] Eh, I got this thing
on sale from the system store.
If I were you,
I wouldn't accept
anything less
than a hundred million.
A hundred mill?
[JINWOO] I only paid
like 3 million gold.
If the store's items
go for this much
I might not even need to sell
the Sphere of Avarice.
[JINWOO] Can I use
your bathroom real quick.
Oh, of course.
[YOONHO] I knew he wasn't
a lightweight by any means.
What I saw
goes far beyond strength.
The magic I sensed
in the assessment lab
the athleticism he showed
outside of it.
Seems he's still improving
even though his reawakening
should have long past,
which would be a first
for hunters.
What if he didn't reawaken?
Can a hunter whose strength
grows over time really exist?
[bird chirping]
[groans]
[JINAH] [sighs]
They finally took a hike.
Now, I can head to school
without being bombarded.
[JINWOO]
By the press?
The Association
must've chased them off.
You suck! Why'd you have to go
and make a huge scene?
-Like, you could've told me you
were gonna be on TV! -Hey, hey!
How's that my fault?
Oh, by the way,
I'm gonna be out
for about a week
starting tomorrow.
What? Again?
For work?
-[doorbell rings]
-Uh.
-Could you people get the f--
-Bro!
Jinho Yoo reporting in, boss!
Your sidekick is back!
Is he a reporter,
or some buddy of yours?
]JINHO] Oh, hi,
you must be Jinwoo's sister!
I'm his reliable
right-hand man, Jinho Yoo!
-[JINAH] Uh-huh.
-Huh!
-Uh...
-This guy and I are going
on that week-long work trip
tomorrow.
Like, as in tomorrow morning?
-What do you mean?
-What do I mean. Y'know?
That job.
[groans]
How could I forget?
This job has been weighing
on my shoulders, unbearably!
Hmm?
[snoring]
[groans]
[JINWOO]
They left, but...
journalists
are nothing if not persistent.
Come forth.
Wait. I thought Tusk
had four bodyguards.
Where's the last one?
Right!
I forgot about that guy,
since I kinda put him
through the ceiling.
Well, whatever.
Three should be fine
since you're all pretty tough.
You, stay behind
and keep watch.
I'm entrusting you with Jinah.
Counting on you.
[JINWOO] I'll take a few more
precautions while I'm at it.
Start your patrol.
Might make the city
a bit safer,
come to think of it.
[water burbling]
[JINHO] Thanks for letting
me stay the night.
You're a real one.
Of course, man, I got you.
But what's your plan
going forward?
It's not like he's forcing you
to move out.
Gotta own up
to the consequences, right?
Anyway, what's this job
at the DS Tower?
Yesterday, you mentioned
it would be a week-long thing.
Yeah, I, uh, guess,
you could call it training.
You're saying you're trying
to get even stronger?
Why do that after earning
an S-rank, though?
[JINWOO]
Why not?
Thanks, Jinho.
I'll be back.
I know.
Stay safe, okay?
[JINWOO]
A ring enchanted with water
a cape with wind.
That'll keep the heat off
nicely.
The Demon's Castle is waiting.
Let's get it.
There's a second part?
"The Demon Monarch, Baran,
resides on the highest floor.
Defeat Baran and collect
his soul." Yeah, yeah.
Rewards are a Rune Stone
for Shadow Exchange!
That sounds
like a necromancy skill!
Better reward than last time!
I'll take the extra motivation.
Time to pick up
where we left off.
Warp to the 75th floor
[SANG-MI]
I can't believe that Jinho
would suddenly pack his bags
and leave home.
Surely you're missing him.
A troublesome child
has stretched his wings
and flown the nest.
What's really surprising
is how long he wait..
[groans]
That's strange.
What's strange, dear?
-[MYUNGHAN] It's getting dark.
-Are you all right?
-[thuds]
-[SANG-MI] Honey!
[rumbling]
[fire roaring]
[stomping]
[JINWOO] Time for a test drive.
You're up, Tusk.
[growls]
[electricity crackling]
♪
[explosion]
Uh!
[JINWOO]
Blown clean off its feet
and that's after
Tusk was nerfed!
I'll be more strategic
with that move in the future.
But yeah, the Sphere of Avarice
is all yours, Tusk.
[MYUNGHAN]
I see.
So, Jinho came to visit.
[SANG-MI]
He did.
I told him
you collapsed from exhaustion.
Ah.
Did you now?
It's the Eternal Sleep Disease?
[MALE DOCTOR] That's correct.
It typically begins
as abrupt spells of drowsiness,
then eventually transitions
into a lasting coma.
And how was I infected
with this disease?
[MALE DOCTOR] Most likely from
prolonged exposure to mana.
It tends to occur in people
with naturally low resistance.
Mister Yoo,
are there any hunters
among your immediate family?
Oh, no!
Oh, honey.
Hmm.
Our son is a hunter.
[MALE DOCTOR]
Granted, we can't be certain
that's the
cause in your case, but...
[rattling]
[MYUNGHAN]
The entire planet
is steeped in magic power
these days,
and I'm intolerant to it.
Hmm.
Is the world rejecting me?
Am I being culled?
[MALE HUNTER 1] Nothing beats
a peaceful afternoon, huh?
[MALE HUNTER 2]
Yeah, you said it.
Wanna use what's left of it
to fish?
We're on patrol.
No slacking, got it?
-Huh?
[MALE HUNTER 2]
What is that?
[seagulls squawking]
[JINWOO] Looks like dispatching
six shadow squads
is already paying off,
good way to be efficient.
I made it pretty simple
by only giving them
two orders to follow.
One, slay every enemy
they encounter in their search.
Two, report to me
if they find an entry permit.
I am missing out
on some loot this way,
but I make much
faster progress in exchange.
Or I was making progress.
We've been
on the 80th floor
for two days.
I just don't get
why the pace slowed down.
[exhales]
Where's the damn permit?
Hm?
Something's destroying
the shadows, and fast.
Looks like it's squad A,
but I didn't think
any of these demons
would be a problem
for my high orcs.
Gotta call 'em back,
they're getting thrashed.
Let's see why, c'mon.
[clothes rustle]
Squad B was also
mysteriously slaughtered
Whatever is responsible
must be pretty fierce.
It's weird, though.
Tusk's squad was the one
closest to squad A
when it went down.
So why go after squad B next?
They're weaker, sure,
but they were further away.
If this enemy realized
they couldn't beat Tusk,
they must possess
some level of intelligence.
And if they're
gauging strength,
I know which squad
they'll target next.
[growls]
♪
[roars]
[groans]
♪
[JINWOO]
Makes sense.
No wonder
my weaker shadow squads
were annihilated.
[spear swinging]
[Jinwoo grunts]
[crashes]
♪
[JINWOO]
You know, I've always wondered.
Do demons like you feel fear?
[footsteps approaching]
[chuckles softly]
You're shaking.
I guess I have my answer.
♪